Hispanic Women's Network of Texas Records
Nettie Lee Benson Latin American Collection
- Part 3: Additions
  - Annual Conferences and Special Events, 1987-2019
    - Annual Conferences, 1988-2019
      - 29th Annual Conference, 2015 (Box 92, Folder 8)
      - 30th Annual Conference, 2016 (Box 92, Folder 9)
      - 31st Annual Conference, 2017 (Box 92, Folder 10)
      - 33rd Annual Conference, 2019 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - Special Events, 1987-2017
      - 1987-2006 (Box 92, Folder 12)
      - 2007-2017 (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Collected Materials
    - Collected Materials, 2004-2012 (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Collected Materials, 2014-2019; undated (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Local Chapters
    - Austin Chapter, 1988-2003
      - Cascio, Marti (VP of Community Relations and Outreach) Binder, 2001-2003 (Box 92, Folder 16-17)
      - City of Austin Solicitation Permit Material, 1988-1998 (Box 92, Folder 18)
      - De Leon, Amelia Binder, 2002-2004 (Box 93, Folder 1-2)
      - Events, 2015; undated (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - Gonzales, Irene - Membership Guide and Resource Book, 2004 June (Box 93, Folder 4)
      - Quinonez, Gloria Binder, 2001-2004 (Box 93, Folder 5-7)
      - Williams, Velia Saenz Binder, 2000-2004 (Box 94, Folder 1-2)
      - Williams, Velia Saenz Files, 1994-2001 (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - Williams, Velia Saenz Files, 2000-2001 (Box 94, Folder 4)
      - Williams, Velia Saenz Files, 2003-2004 (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - Williams, Velia Saenz Files, 2004-2005 (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - Williams, Velia Saenz Files, 2002-2005 (Box 95, Folder 1)
      - Williams, Velia Saenz Files, 2004-2005 (Box 95, Folder 2-3)
    - Corpus Christi Chapter, Flores, Almira Binder, 2001-2003 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Corpus Christi Chapter, Flores, Almira Binder, 2001-2003 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Fort Worth Chapter, Latinas in Progress: Educational/Leadership Program, 2007 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - University of Texas Chapter, Happy Hour, 2018 September 4 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - San Antonio Chapter, Flyers, 2008; 2009 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Memorabilia
    - Escamilla, Linda - Letter, Memo, and Photographs for Vision newsletter, 1992 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Escamilla, Linda - conference badges, name holder, and key chains, 1992; 2016-2017 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Nadler, Martha Hinojosa - nametag, undated (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Scrapbook, 1997 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Oversized Material
    - Caller-Times, 2012 July 29 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Cesar Chavez March for Unity Posters, 2002 March 30 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Texas State Legislature Resolutions, 2015; 2018,; undated (Box 97, Folder 3)